Contact

dev.pedroricardo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/opedroricardo (LinkedIn) pedroricardo.vercel.app/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

React.js

Vue.js

Node.js

Languages

Japonês (Elementary)

Português (Native or Bilingual)

Inglês (Full Professional)

Espanhol (Limited Working)

Certifications

HMTL5 e CSS3 parte 4: Avançando no CSS

HTML5 e CSS3 parte 2:

Posicionamento, listas e navegação

HTML5 e CSS3 parte 3:

Trabalhando com formulários e tabelas

labelas

HMTL5 e CSS3 parte 1: A primeira página da Web

Pedro Ricardo Almeida

Full Stack Developer

Santos, São Paulo, Brazil

Summary

I develop high-end software with continuous integration/delivery.

Since 2019, my career has been focused on teaching people and learning with them, helping companies to improve their profits.

Since 2021, I have studied and used Vue, React, Node, their main libraries, and frameworks.

I'm also interested in AWS, Python, and Elixir for my career evolution.

Experience

YBOH

2 years 9 months

Full Stack Developer

December 2021 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Santos, São Paulo, Brazil

I had the oportunity to develop and operate on big projects for Mercedes Benz and other brazilian big companies. Currently I lead a developer team and develop high-end software with continuous integration/delivery.

Front End Intern

July 2021 - December 2021 (6 months)

Santos, São Paulo, Brasil

As an intern, I learned Vue's and Node's basis.

codeBuddy agora é SuperGeeks

IT Instructor

January 2019 - June 2021 (2 years 6 months)

Santos, São Paulo, Brasil

When I was 15 years old, I worked on projects like Co.Lab at RedHat and Positive Agenda at Carrefour's Bank. I also taught programming logic for children and teenagers at codeBuddy

Education

Colégio Santa Cecília

Ensino Médio · (January 2019 - November 2021)